<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Suyog&#39;s personal blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Suyog&#39;s personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:07:28 +0545</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How a Python Decorator Crashed My Flask App: Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-decorator-broke-my-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:07:28 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-decorator-broke-my-app/</guid>
      <description>Python decorators are wonderful. They let you modify or extend the behavior of functions or methods without permanently modifying their source code. I&amp;rsquo;ve used them in several places in my code to add features to my functions. But recently, I came across a weird, or rather interesting, bug that I felt was worth sharing.
The Issue So I had a Flask API that was responsible for ML inference. Here is what the rough structure of the project looked like:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Tuning with DSPy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dspy-prompt-tuning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 12:48:50 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dspy-prompt-tuning/</guid>
      <description>What is it and why is it needed? Last week, I spent some time writing prompts for classifying documents into a fixed set of classes based on their OCR text. I spent some time tweaking and experimenting with the prompt for the model to behave exactly how I wanted it to behave. But prompt tuning, for those who have tried it, knows how painfully daunting it is to make these models behave exactly how you&amp;rsquo;d like them to behave&amp;hellip; that also consistently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:20:58 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/now/</guid>
      <description>A short synopsis of my &amp;ldquo;now&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:54:59 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! First of all, welcome to my blog. I&amp;rsquo;m just an ordinary developer from Kathmandu, Nepal. My experience lies in developing AI-based software solutions. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m working as an ML Engineer at Docsumo, a document-AI company. My day-to-day job involves exploring various ML models for extracting information from documents. In addition to research, I also develop, deploy, and monitor these systems in production.
Before working at Docsumo, I ventured into entrepreneurship while still in college.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started ... Again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:54:59 +0545</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Hello to Everyone Reading This, It&amp;rsquo;s been quite a while since I last penned anything down. The last memory I have of writing was during my GRE&amp;rsquo;s Analytical Writing Assessment (AWA) — ah, the good ol&amp;rsquo; days! But let’s set the jokes aside for a moment. I used to write articles and courses for The Click Reader for over a year. However, after moving on from Click Reader, my writing habits took an unexpected hiatus.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
